Three weeks have passed since the wheels of fate
began to turn for Tachibana Junichi and Nakata Sae.
〈橘純一と中多紗江の
運命の歯車が動き出してから〉
〈３週間が　たっていた〉
Um...
（紗江）ええっと…
秋になってくると
A-Aren't warm drinks nice when fall comes around?
温かい飲み物が　いいですね
Like sweet-bean soup, or corn soup...
お汁粉とか　コーンスープとか
Or maybe cocoa...
ココアとか　その…
Um...
I-I prefer milk tea.
私は　ミルクティーが好きなんです
ミルクティーを　いただけますか？
Could I have some milk tea?
Her training for her job interview
is starting to bear fruit thanks to him.
〈少女の
アルバイトの面接試験の特訓は〉
〈少年のおかげで
成果が見え始めていた〉
In particular, her communication skills are almost at a passable level.
〈特に　コミュニケーション能力においては〉
〈ほぼ合格点に達したと
いってよい〉
〈ただし　それは〉
However, that's only if she's talking to a vending machine.
〈相手が自動販売機の場合に
かぎってなのだが〉
はあ～ッ
（梨穂子）ねえ
まだ決まらないの？
Hey, are you still deciding?
あッ　すみません　お先にどうぞ
Sorry.  Please go ahead.
Really?  Thanks!
ホント？　ありがとう
わ～ッ　もうホットがあるんだ
Wow, they already have warm drinks in there.
I wonder when they swapped them in.  Don't you?
一体いつ入れ替えるのかな？
ね～ッ
不思議だよね～　よ～し
パンダココア買っちゃおっと
It's a real mystery.
Okay, I'm gonna get Panda Cocoa!
（薫）ねえ　今の何？
（純一）特訓だよ
Hey, what was all that about?
Training.
I know she's shy and all, but do you
really think she's ready for the interview?
人見知りとは聞いてたけど
バイトの面接　大丈夫なの？
I'll figure something out.
まあ　何とかするさ
先は長そうね～
You have a long way to go.
まあ　頑張ってちょうだい
うわッ
Anyway, give it your all.
Nakata-san.
中多さん
あッ　教官
Instructor.
As long as you're talking to vending machines, it looks like your conversations skills pass.
自販機相手なら
ほぼ合格点だね
でも　あまり会話が
うまくいかなくて…
But I can't really seem to make the conversation go anywhere...
It would be pretty scary if it did...
〈それで　うまくいったら
いったで怖い〉
そろそろ本当に食堂のおばさんと
会話してみたらどうかな？
Wanna try having a real conversation with one of the cafeteria ladies?
えッ　でも…
But...
教官　私　まだ…
I-Instructor, I'm still not...
大丈夫　今の中多さんなら
きっと　できるよ
You'll be fine.
You can definitely do it now after all that training.
Yes, Instructor.
はい　教官
うん
Good.
〈こうして
少年に背中を押された少女は〉
Thus, he encouraged her to tread into the
unknown territory of speaking with the cafeteria ladies.
〈食堂のおばさんとの会話という〉
〈未知なる領域に足を踏み入れる
ことになるのであった〉
・～
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
Ichinichi no hajimari to
１日の始まりと
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
終わりにはいつも傍に
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
あなたがいる　そんな毎日
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
目を覚ませば温かい
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
コーヒー入れて待ってる
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
あなたの左腕に抱きついた
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
会える日まで指折り数えていた
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
今じゃ会えない日の方が少ないね
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
こんな幸せ誰が予想した
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
あなたと私がそう
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
恋をした
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
愛してる　あなたのこと
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
初めてのキモチよ
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
愛してる　ずっとずっと
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
変わらないキモチ
My feelings will never change
Here's your lunch set A.
（おばさん）はい　Ａランチ
・（生徒）ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
さあ　中多さん
はッ　はい
Go ahead, Nakata-san.
Y-Yes.
Don't worry, they aren't gonna eat you.
大丈夫
とって食われるわけじゃないし
In fact, we're the ones who'll be eating our lunch here.
むしろ
昼ごはんを食べるのは僕達だよ
〈意味不明である〉
That made no sense.
分かりました
行ってきます
Okay.
Nakata Sae Arc
Chapter 2
Training
Off I go.
Yes?
うん？
あッ　あの…
はいよ　何にするの？
U-Um...
Yes, what can I get you?
あの　その…
Uh, well...
あッ　あの…
うん？　どうしたの？
U-Um...
Hmm?  What's the matter?
あッ　その…
Uh... well...
まだ決まってないの？
You haven't decided yet?
U-Um... yeah.
あッ　あの…　はい
Well then, just call me over when you're ready.
じゃあ　決まったら呼んでね
あッ…
すみません　教官
I'm so sorry, Instructor.
いいかい中多さん
あそこにいるのは人じゃない
Listen, Nakata-san.
They're not actual people.
おばさん型　自動販売機だ
えッ？
They're just cafeteria lady-style vending machines!
Huh?
Cafeteria ladies across the country, please forgive his rude comment.
〈全国の食堂のおばさん　少年の
失礼な発言をお許しのほど〉
試しに
そうやって考えてごらん
Just try and imagine that, okay?
あッ　教官
自販機に見えました！
Instructor!  I see her as a vending machine!
さあ　もう一度挑戦だ！
はい
All right, now try again!
Okay!
Ah, excuse me...
あッ　あの…
はいよ
えっと
Yes?
Um...
Isn't it a little cold today?
The cafeteria ladies Nakata Sae
is seeing right now are not
actually vending machines.
今日は少し寒いですね
Yes, it's almost fall.
そうだね　そろそろ秋だからね
Washing the dishes must be tough when it gets colder.
寒くなると
洗い物が大変そうですよね
It sure is!
そうなのよ～　まあ
ここは食器洗い機があるから
Well, we've got dishwashers here, so it's not that bad.
まだマシなんだけどね
そうなんですか
I see...
Thanks for your concern all the same.
心配してくれてありがとうね
あッ　はい
Y-Yes.
では　失礼します
Well, excuse me.
またね～
See you.
どうでしたでしょうか？
H-How did I do?
ぎこちないながらも
よく話せてたと思うよ
It was a little stiff, but I think you did well.
Really?
本当ですか？
うん
Yeah.
もちろん　まだまだ
会話も唐突で粗削りだったけど
Of course, the conversation was still quite random and rough,
but it was definitely the most natural of them all so far.
今までの中では一番　自然だったね
はッ　はい
Y-Yes.
Let's call that one a success for now.
とりあえずは
成功と思っていいんじゃないかな
ありがとうございます
これからも頑張ろうね
Thank you so much.
Let's keep it up.
はい
よろしくお願いします　教官
Yes.
Please continue to teach me, Instructor.
〈このとき　少年も少女も〉
At the time, neither of them realized they hadn't ordered anything.
〈肝心の注文が
できていなかったことには〉
〈全く気づいてないのであった〉
This is today's training area.
〈ここが　本日の特訓会場である〉
After the coffee incident, they were prohibited from training at home.
〈あのコーヒーの一件が
あってから〉
〈少年は自宅での特訓を
禁止されていたのである〉
〈というか　むしろ学校の方が
マズイのではないだろうか？〉
Though training at school would probably be worse.
そろそろ中多さんの来る頃だな
Nakata-san should be here soon.
（ドアが開く）
さあ　始めようか
（詞）橘君？
All right, let's start.
Tachibana-kun?
えッ？
何を始めるの？
What are we starting?
あッ　いや別に…
綾辻さん　どうしたの？
Oh... uh, nothing.
What are you doing here, Ayatsuji-san?
うん　これを返却しておくよう
頼まれちゃって
Oh, I was asked to return these.
じゃあ　お先に失礼
All right, see you later.
Yeah, good work.
ああ　ご苦労さま
（ドアが閉まる）
Man, she surprised me.
あ～ッ　ビックリした
あッ　そういえば中多さん
今日は掃除当番だった
Oh yeah, Nakata-san's on cleaning duty today.
今日は機敏な行動を
特訓しようと思う
We're going to do some agility training today.
Okay.
はい
バイトでは常に
They'll need you to be fast at your job.
素早い行動が求められるはずだ
はい　教官
Y-Yes, Instructor.
というわけで
今日の特訓は早着替えだ！
And so...
Today's training will be speed-changing!
えッ？
早着替えだよ　中多さん
Speed-changing, Nakata-san!
Speed... changing?
早着替えですか？
そう
Yes, changing quickly into your work uniform.
バイトの制服に素早く着替えること
とても大事なことだよ
It's very important.
あッ　はい
そうですね…
Uh... yes.
I guess you're right...
じゃあ早速　始めよう
着替えは持ってきたよね？
All right, let's get started!
Did you bring the clothes?
あッ　はい
教官に言われたとおり
Yes.
I did just as you asked, Instructor.
よし　じゃあまずは
制服から体操服への早着替えだ！
Good.
Then let's begin with speed-changing
from your uniform into your P.E. clothes!
ここでですか？
H-Here?
ほら　その机に隠れれば
見えないから大丈夫だよ
Well, I won't be able to see you if you do it behind that desk.  Don't worry.
でも　誰か来ちゃうかも
しれないですし…
B-But...
S-Someone might come...
それなんだよ　中多さん！
えッ？
That's the point, Nakata-san!
Huh?
より　実戦に近い状況での
特訓が役に立つんだ！
Training in realistic situations is the most effective!
どういうことですか？
What do you mean?
I'm talking about tension!
緊張感だよ
緊張感？
T-Tension?
実際のバイトはもっと大変だし
すごく緊張する環境だと思う
A real job is going to be even harder.
It'll be a very stressful environment.
Getting properly changed in time...
時間内に
キチンとした格好に着替える
それが早着替え特訓だ　誰が来るか
なんて気にしてたらダメだよ
That's the point of speed-changing training.
You can't be worried about somebody coming along!
R-Really?
そうなんですか？
ああ
〈それにしても　この少年〉
Yeah.
I'm amazed at this guy.
〈アルバイトの経験が
全くないにもかかわらず〉
He's never even had a job, so how does he talk with such confidence?
〈どうして　こう
熱く語れるのだろうか？〉
分かってくれたかな？
はい　分かりました
Do you understand now?
Yes, I think get it!
All right, then let's get started!
それじゃ始めるぞ　まずは体操服だ
はい！
Let's begin with PE clothes!
Yes!
〈なぜ　体操服なのだ？〉
Why PE clothes?
And does "begin with" mean there's more to come?
〈そして　「まず」ということは
次があるのか？〉
さあ　準備して
はッ　はい
Okay, get ready.
Y-Yes!
じゃあ中多さん　いくよ
設定はバイトの日だというのに
Okay Nakata-san, here we go.
Here's the scenario.
You've got work today, but you got absorbed in a conversation with Miya after school and left late.
放課後　美也と話し込んで
学校を出るのが遅くなった
シフトの時間が迫ってる
制服に着替えてタイムカードを押すまで
The start of your shift draws near.
You've only got three minutes to
change and punch your time card.
残り　あと３分しかない
いいかな？
Are you ready?
はい
よ～い　スタート！
Yes.
Ready...
Start!
２分経過　あと残り１分
どこまで着替えられてるかな？
Two minutes have passed.  Only one minute left!
How far have you gotten?
上は着替えました　あとは下を…
よし　頑張れ
I've changed my top.  Just the pants now...
O-Okay, keep it up!
あれッ　これ前と後ろが…
Huh?  Did I get it backwards?
あれッ？　えっと…
遅いぞ　急ぐんだ！
Huh?  Um...
You're slowing down!  Hurry!
Y-Yes!
はッ　はい！
お待たせしました　教官
よし
I'm done, Instructor!
All right.
時間内に着替えられたね
でも　ちゃんと着替えられたか
You changed within the time limit.
However, I need to make sure your clothes are on properly.
服装の確認をする
お願いします
P-Please do.
All right, check complete!
よし　チェック完了　ＯＫだ
Looks okay.
Now...
では　ジャージの下を脱いで！
Take your pants off!
〈なぜ　脱がせる？〉
Why is he telling her to undress?
はい！
Yes!
And why is she doing it?!
〈そして　なぜ脱ぐ？〉
I took them off...
脱ぎました…
All right...
よし　次は水着だ！
はい！
Next is your swimsuit!
Okay!
〈だから　なぜ水着？〉
Wait, why a swimsuit?!
スタート！
Start!
Um...
えっと…
えっと…　あれッ？
U-Um... huh?
お待たせしました
I'm done!
ああッ　あッ！
うわッ
ああッ…
（美也）ごめ～ん
来るの遅くなっちゃった
Sorry!
I'm a little late-
〈妹の目に飛び込んできたのは〉
She was met with the sight of her brother
groping her friend's breasts over her swimsuit.
〈水着姿の親友の胸を
わしづかみにしている〉
〈兄の姿だった〉
Nii-nii...
にぃに…　何やってんの～！
What do you think you're doing?!
（純一が美也に　ひっかかれる）
I see.
（逢）そうなんだ
中多さん頑張ってるね
You're working hard, Nakata-san.
美也ちゃんと橘先輩のおかげなの
It's all thanks to Miya-chan and Tachibana-senpai.
That's not true at all.
そんなことないよ
逢ちゃんも部活　頑張ってるよね
Aren't you working hard in your club too, Ai-chan?
うん
２人とも頑張ってるね～
Yeah.
You're both such hard workers.
すごい　すごい！
美也も何か頑張ろうかな
It's amazing!
Maybe I should try do to something too.
そうだ　美也は
２人の応援　頑張っちゃう！
I know, I'll cheer you guys on!
２人の応援隊長になろ～っと
I'll be your cheering team captain!
（はるか）アハッ　かわいい～
So cute!
私はそんな応援隊長を
応援してあげるわ
I'll cheer for the cheering team captain!
はあ～ッ　何てキュートなの
森島先輩？
Geez, you're so cute!
Morishima-senpai?
これが隊長の感触なのね
So this is what a captain feels like...
うん
Yes.
特別特訓の場所が決まったな
I know where our next training session will be.
Sign: Koedo Hot Spring Adventure
あッ
ごめ～ん　待たせちゃったかな？
Sorry!
Were you waiting?
いえ　私も今
来たばかりですから
No, I just got here myself.
そっか　よかった
I see.  Thank goodness.
まったく
美也が寝坊するから遅刻だよ
Geez, the reason we're late is because Miya overslept.
I set my alarm, but I just couldn't get up.
だって　目覚ましかけたんだけど
起きられなくて
遅くまで
マンガ読んだりしてるからだろ
That's because you stayed up late reading manga.
だって「ビーバー三国志」読みだしたら
やめられなくなっちゃった
But I couldn't stop reading Beaver Romance of the Three Kingdoms once I started!
Well, you didn't have to read it last night.
だから　別に昨日読まなくても…
遅れて　ごめんね
ホントに　ごめんなさい
Sorry we're late.
I'm really sorry.
大丈夫ですよ
ホント？　ありがとう　じゃあ行こうか
Don't worry about it.
Really?  Thanks.
Well, let's go.
Yeah.
うん
あの　ここって…
Um, isn't this place...
そう　温泉だよ　ここで特訓だ！
That's right, it's a hot spring.
This is where you're training!
えッ？
にしし～ッ　温泉楽しみ
What?
I can't wait!
はい
Okay.
I read about this weird bath they have here from a magazine.
この間　雑誌で見たけど
変わった温泉があるらしいんだ
変わった温泉ですか？
Weird bath?
Yeah.
うん　今日はそこで特訓するよ
Today's training will take place there.
はい
美也　こういうとこ初めて～
Okay.
This is the first time I've been to a place like this!
あッ　水着持ってきたよね？
You brought your swimsuits, right?
はい
じゃあ　水着に着替えたら
Yes.
Well then, we'll meet at the footbath corner once you're done changing.
中の足湯コーナーに集合ね
了解！
Gotcha!
Footbath Corner
お待たせ
Sorry I took so long.
Huh?  Nii-nii, why aren't you in a swimsuit?
あれッ　どうして
にぃには水着じゃないの？
Nobody would want to see me in one.
誰も嬉しくないからだよ
（美也・紗江）うん？
〈少年は
よ～く分かっているのであった〉
He really gets it.
Nakata-san, that swimsuit...
中多さん　その水着…
似合ってるね
...looks good on you.
えッ　ホントですか？
Huh?  R-Really?
Yeah, it really suits you.
うん　すごく似合ってると思うよ
ありがとうございます
美也ちゃんのおかげです
Thank you.
It's thanks to Miya.
えッ　何で美也のおかげなの？
Huh?  How is it thanks to Miya?
Nii-nii, I've always known exactly what you like.
にぃにの好みなんて
お見通しなんだから
前に　にぃにの部屋に
置いてあった雑…
The mag you left in your room the other day-
あの　似合ってるって
言ってもらえて
Um...
I'm really happy that... you think it looks good on me.
ホントに嬉しいです
Well, let's get going.
じゃあ　行こうか
はい
O-Okay.
Doctor Fish Corner
Whoa, there's so many of them.
・（美也）うわ～ッ　いっぱいいるね
All these fishes swimming around in the bath...
お湯の中にお魚が泳いでる…
They're called Doctor Fishes.
ドクターフィッシュって
いってね
リラックス効果や
マッサージ効果があるんだって
Apparently they help you relax.  It's like getting a massage.
They also do all sorts of good things to your body, like removing excess keratin from your skin.
それと　肌の余分な角質を
取ってくれたり
色々　体にいいらしいんだ
そうなんですか？
Really?
ふ～ん
早速　入ってみる？
Let's try putting our feet in.
うん
Okay.
大丈夫だよ
こんなに小さな魚だから
It'll be fine.  These fishes are tiny.
It's also my first time doing this, actually.
でも　実は
僕も初めてなんだ
えッ　そうなんですか？
うん　足湯だから
Really?
Yeah.
This is a footbath, so you just need to put your feet in.
足だけ入れればいいんだって
はい
Okay.
Whoa, this feels kinda weird.
うわあッ
こりゃ何とも不思議な感じだね
アハハハッ　くすぐったいよ
すごい　一斉に足に集まってきたぞ
It tickles!
Wow, they're all gathering at our feet.
Whoa, what's this?
うわ～ッ　何これ？
ヒャッ！
あッ　ダメ！
えッ？
Ah, no!
Huh?
ああッ　足　足の…
足の？
Ah, my... my toes...
Y-Your toes?
They're going between my toes, and...
指の間に入ってきて…
ヒャッ　ダメ　ダ…
Oh, no!
くすぐったい
あッ…　許してください
It tickles...
No more...
あッ！
中多さん？
Nakata-san?
Sae-chan sounds kinda erotic right now.
紗江ちゃん　ちょっとエッチっぽいね
確かに…
Y-You're right...
It tickles...
くすぐったい　ダメーッ！
No!
さあ　特別特訓を始めるよ
All right, let's start the special training!
えッ　ここでですか？
ああッ！
H-Here?
バイトの模擬面接試験をする
いいかい？
We'll have a mock interview.  Ready?
はッ　はい
まず　名前は？
Y-Yes.
What is your name?
中多紗江です　あッ！
N-Nakata Sae.
学校はどこ？　何年生？
What school do you go to?  What year are you in?
輝日東高校　１年です
I'm a f-freshman at Kibitou high school.
あッ　また指の間に…　ああッ
Ah, they're going between my toes again...
ダメダメ　足を出したら失格だよ
あッ　はい　すみません
Nope.  You fail if you pull your feet out.
Okay, I'm sorry.
ヒャッ！　くすぐったい
It tickles...
中多さん？
あッ…
Nakata-san?
ああッ…
ハアハアハア…
ああ…
あッ！
It's the master of this hot spring!
この温泉の主だ！
大変だ　中多さんが襲われる！
This is bad!  It'll attack Nakata-san!
あッ！
先輩…　先輩！
Senpai... Senpai!
中多さん！
先輩　先輩！
Nakata-san!
Senpai.  Senpai!
せんぱ～い！
中多さん！
Senpai!
Nakata-san!
中多さ～ん！
せんぱ～い！
Senpai!
う～ん
先輩？　先輩？
Senpai?  Senpai?
大丈夫ですか？
えッ？
Are you okay?
Huh?
You passed out at the footbath...
先輩　足湯で　のぼせちゃって…
そうだったんだ…
I see.
〈少年が　のぼせたのは
足湯のせいではない〉
The footbath wasn't the reason he passed out though.
Fruits
Here.
これ　どうぞ
ありがとう
Thanks.
Huh?  Where did Miya go?
あれッ　美也は？
お土産売り場を見にいってます
She's taking a look at the souvenir shop.
I see...
そっか…
うん？　何ですか？
Hmm?  What is it?
あッ　なんでもない…
Nothing...
（美也の寝息）
美也ちゃん　よく眠ってますね
Miya-chan's fast asleep.
うん　そうだね
はあ～ッ
Yeah, she is.
あの　模擬面接の結果は…
Um, how did I do in the mock interview?
うん　今日は
よく頑張ったから合格
Ah, yes.  You did a good job today, so you pass.
Yay!
よかった～
But please train me more.
でも　もっと鍛えてください
まだ足りない？
はい
Still don't feel ready yet?
Yes.
Well then, let's continue training at my place.
じゃあ　うちで
もうひともみしてあげよう
はい　教官
Yes, Instructor.
〈少年は　まだ知らなかった〉
He had yet to realize why she wanted more training from him.
〈少女がなぜ　少年にもっと
鍛えてもらいたかったのかを〉
（美也）ねえ　紗江ちゃんもいるから
ちょっとだけやらない？
Hey, let's play this for a bit since Sae-chan's here!
Easy Millionaire Game
is easy!!
Easy stage
Basic stage
Life has mountains and valleys
Let's live an easy life and aim to be a billionaire
これ　確か親戚で一番お金持ちの
おじさんにもらったんだよな
Didn't we get this from our richest uncle?
Yeah, he told us to get lots of practice from it so we can be rich like him.
おじさんみたいに　お金もうけが
うまくなるよう練習しなさいって
Yeah, I think I remember.
ああ　何となく思い出してきたぞ
Come on, let's play.
ねえ　やろうよ
うん
にししッ　にぃには
これ弱いんだよね～
Okay.
You're pretty bad at this game, Nii-nii.
紗江ちゃんもいい？
うん
Sae-chan, wanna play too?
Okay.
そんなに難しくないし　ルールは
やりながら覚えていけばいいし
It's not a difficult game, and you can learn the rules as we play.
美也の方こそ
ルールは覚えてるんだろうな？
What about you, Miya?  Do you still remember the rules?
もちろん！　え～っと
順番にサイコロを振って
Of course!
Um, we take turns rolling the dice and go around the board.
同じところをグルグル回る
で？
お金をためる
まあ　簡単にいえばそうだな
And?
We collect money.
Well, that's pretty much it in a nutshell.
Well then, rock, paper, scissors!
じゃあ　ジャンケンポン
In other words, this game is like a miniature copy of one's life.
〈えてして　この手のゲームは
人生の縮図といってよい〉
Scissors!
A goat ate the neighbor's hedge.
Pay ¥100,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
A goat ate the neighbor's hedge.
Pay ¥100,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
A goat ate the neighbor's hedge.
Pay ¥100,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
A goat ate the neighbor's hedge.
Pay ¥100,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
Pay ¥5,000,000 to
expand your business.
High-quality Shiitake
mushroom field in
Oita. You may
purchase this for
¥2,000,000 if
no other player has
already purchased it.
An envoy from space has arrived.
Spend ¥500,000 on a reception.
Pay ¥5,000,000 to
expand your business.
え～っと　何なに
「大分の高級しいたけ畑」
Pay ¥5,000,000 to
expand your business.
Hmm, let's see...
"High-quality Shiitake mushroom field in Oita."
「誰も持ってない場合は
２００万円で購入できる」
"You may purchase this for two million yen if no other player has already purchased it."
Wow, this Shiitake mushroom field is pretty expensive.
へえ～ッ　しいたけ畑って高いね
うん
Yeah.
No, it also says "You must pay the owner, if there is one, a hundred thousand yen for the Shiitake mushrooms."
いやいや「所有者がいた場合は
高級しいたけ代として」
「１０万円を所有者に支払う」
ってあるし
こういう安定した物件が
大事なんだよ　よし　僕は買うぞ
It's good property that will give me steady income.
All right, I'm buying it!
All right, here I go!
よ～し　バンバンいくよ　えいッ！
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
おッ　不動産のマスだな
A real estate square.
「新築マンションを
５００万円で買える」　い～らない！
"You may purchase this newly constructed apartment for 5 million yen."
Don't want it!
いいのか？
新築は人気物件だけど
You sure?  Newly constructed property is popular.
チッチッチ　分かってないな～
You don't get it at all.
イベントカードであっという間に値段が
下がる新築マンションは買わないよ
I'm not gonna buy a newly constructed mansion
that will instantly drop in price with an event card.
そうなの？
資産運用は慎重に
I-It can?
Be careful when investing in property.
にししッ
美也ちゃん　すごいね
Miya-chan, you're amazing.
さあ　紗江ちゃんの番だよ
It's your turn now, Sae-chan.
あッ　イベントカードひけるよ
えッ　何　何？
You can draw an event card!
Hey, what does it say?
"You make your debut as a writer after winning the newcomer-novelist award."
「新人小説家賞で大賞を受賞して
小説家デビュー」
「処女作が
大ベストセラーで印税が入る」
"Your first release is such a bestseller that you receive royalties from it."
「その印税で個人の出版社を設立」
だって
"You use these royalties to establish your own publishing firm."
紗江ちゃん　すご～い！
いきなり大富豪だ
Sae-chan, amazing!
You've become a multi-millionaire right at the start!
すごいね　中多さん
はい
That's incredible, Nakata-san.
Y-Yes.
All right, my turn!
よし　次　僕だ
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
However, kids cannot play it
due to it receiving an M rating.
You lose all the money you invested.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
However, kids cannot play it
due to it receiving an M rating.
You lose all the money you invested.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
However, kids cannot play it
due to it receiving an M rating.
You lose all the money you invested.
What is it?
何なに「さっき投資した
ゲーム会社のゲームが無事完成」
"The game company you have just invested in has successfully produced a game."
"However, kids cannot play it due to it receiving an M rating."
「なぜかＺ指定を受けて
子供が買えない」
"You lose all the money you invested."
「投資したお金は
一切戻ってこない」
えッ？
わあッ　失敗？
Ah, you failed?
いや　完成はしたぞ
でも　お金戻ってこないんでしょ？
Well no, the game was completed.
But you lost the money you invested.
まあな…
失敗じゃん　失敗　失敗！
I-I guess.
Then you failed!  You failed, you failed!
いいんだよ　ゲームが完成したって
ことは男のロマンは貫いたんだから
Whatever!  To produce a game is
every man's dream, and I did that!
お金じゃないんだよ！
It's not about the money!
〈やはり　この手のボードゲームは
現実とリンクしているもののようだ〉
It really does seem that this board game is linked to reality.
Oh no, we got too into the game and it's gotten late...
いけない　ゲームに夢中になってて
すっかり遅くなったな
特訓がまだ…
あッ
We haven't trained yet...
今日は土曜だし泊まっていけば？
紗江ちゃん
Since it's a Saturday, why don't you stay the night, Sae-chan?
えッ　いいの？
Is it really okay?
We don't mind at all, so call your parents and ask.
うちは全然大丈夫だから
おうちの人に電話して
聞いてみたら？
うん　そうしたら？
Yeah, do that.
はい
紗江ちゃんのお父さん
Okay.
Sae-chan's dad is a little protective, so I hope he won't be mad.
ちょっと過保護なんだって
怒られないかな？
My dad said I can.
お父さん　いいって
やった～！
Yay!
紗江ちゃんの胸
やっぱり　おっきいね～
Sae-chan, your boobs are really big.
Really?
そうかな…
Wow, awesome!
わ～ッ　すごいね　浮いてる
浮いてる　美也のは浮かないよ～
They're floating, they're floating!
Mine don't float.
They're three times...
美也の３倍　いや４倍？
No, four times my size?
まんま肉まんの２倍くらいかな？
They're probably twice the size of a meat bun...
えッ　まんま肉まん？
ホント　紗江ちゃんは
Huh?  Meat bun?
Sae-chan, your body's really soft!
フカフカボディーだね
キャッ
And here he is wishing he could be the soap in the bath.
〈できれば　風呂場の石けんにでも
なりたいと願う少年であったが〉
Unfortunately for him, it won't happen.
〈残念ながら
それは無理なのだった〉
あッ…　そのパジャマ
Those pajamas...
美也ちゃんに借りました
Miya-chan lent them to me.
中多さんが着ると　美也が
着てるときとは印象が違うね
They look pretty different on you than they do on Miya.
えッ　似合ってませんか？
They don't look good on me?
No, they do.
ううん
似合ってる　かわいいよ
It's cute.
It makes me want another little sister just like you, Nakata-san.
中多さんみたいな妹が
もう１人欲しいなって思うよ
私はイヤです
えッ？
I don't want that.
Huh?
I don't want to...
私は妹じゃ…
妹じゃイヤです
I don't want to be your little sister.
What?
えッ？
Their wheels of fate are on the verge of spinning even faster.
〈２人の運命の歯車は　今〉
〈大きく動き出そうと
しているのだった〉
・～
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
会いたい気持ちでなぞる指くるくる
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
合えない午後なら浮かべるはフワフワ
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
Anata no koto omou dake de
あなたの事想うだけで
Just thinking about you
Watashi shiawase desu
私幸せです
Makes me so happy
Ippai oshaberi shitakute
いっぱいお喋りしたくて
I want to have long chats with you
Ima sugu ni
今すぐに
Right away
Itsumo futarikiri dattara
いつも二人きりだったら
If only we could always be alone together
Ii no ni na
いいのにな
It would be so nice
Tsugi ni au made wa sukoshi oazuke tsurai kedo
次に合うまでは少しお預け辛いけど
It'll be hard to wait until the next time we can meet
Motto daisuki ni nareru hazu ne
もっと大好きになれるはずね
But in the meantime I'll grow to love you even more
Nareru hazu ne
なれるはずね
I'll love you even more
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
会いたい気持ちでなぞる指くるくる
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
会えない午後なら浮かべるはフワフワ
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
My Darling itsumo soba ni itai
マイダーリン　いつも側に居たい
My darling, I want to always be by your side
Zutto anata shika mienai wa
ずっとあなたしか見えないわ
I'll never look at anyone but you
Daisuki yo
大好きよ
I love you
Preview
Next episode preview.
Nii-nii, didn't Sae-chan sound really erotic when those fishes were poking her feet?
W-What are you saying?!
I was just training her.
I wasn't thinking about anything like that.
Oh?
Then why couldn't you take your eyes off Sae-chan's boobs, Nii-nii?
W-Well...
Next episode: "Change".
Next Episode
Change
I wonder what Nakata-san meant with those words.
Someone as thick as you wouldn't understand, Nii-nii.